<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-29T21:34:49+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Health App</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>Digital Society School</name></author><entry><title type="html">Healthy Dinner Ideas For Two</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nutrition/evidence/based/2019/10/28/Healthy-Dinner-Ideas-For-Two.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Healthy Dinner Ideas For Two" /><published>2019-10-28T08:33:45+01:00</published><updated>2019-10-28T08:33:45+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nutrition/evidence/based/2019/10/28/Healthy-Dinner-Ideas-For-Two</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nutrition/evidence/based/2019/10/28/Healthy-Dinner-Ideas-For-Two.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Hello there&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s common to feel rushed at dinnertime and opt for easy options, such as fast food or frozen meals, even if you’re sharing a meal with just one other person — such as a partner, child, friend, or parent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you crave variety and want to spice up your routine, plenty of scrumptious, small-batch dinners take very little time to prepare and are incredibly healthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, home-cooked meals are associated with improved diet quality, and family meals lead to healthier diets and less weight gain in children and adolescents (1Trusted Source, 2Trusted Source).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are 12 nutritious and scrumptious dinner ideas for two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-chicken-quinoa-bowl&quot;&gt;1. Chicken-quinoa bowl&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This quinoa bowl is packed with protein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a 3.5-ounce (100-gram) serving, quinoa provides all of the essential amino acids, a good proportion of omega-6 fats, and 10% of the Daily Value (DV) for folate (3Trusted Source, 4Trusted Source, 5Trusted Source, 6Trusted Source).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicken is not only low in fat but also high in protein, with 3.5 ounces (100 grams) of breast meat offering 28 grams of protein and 4 grams of fat (7Trusted Source).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-sesame-tofu-fried-rice&quot;&gt;2. Sesame-tofu ‘fried’ rice&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The healthy secret about this fried-rice dish is that it’s actually baked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, tofu has been linked to multiple health benefits, including improved fat metabolism, heart health, and blood sugar control (9Trusted Source, 10Trusted Source, 11Trusted Source, 12Trusted Source, 13Trusted Source).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is vegetarian, although you can swap the tofu for chicken or shrimp if you prefer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Digital Society School</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Don’t Like Meditating. Here’s Why I Do It Anyway</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/03/25/meditation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Don’t Like Meditating. Here’s Why I Do It Anyway" /><published>2019-03-25T18:33:45+01:00</published><updated>2019-03-25T18:33:45+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/03/25/meditation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2019/03/25/meditation.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t like meditating. But when I do it regularly, life is better. Stress is lower. My health improves. Problems seem smaller. I seem bigger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As much as I’m loath to admit it, I’m not a fan of meditation. It comes unnaturally to me, despite my 36 years of martial arts study and interest in self-improvement, health-hacking, and general enlightenment.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I realize this speaks poorly of me as a person, kind of like my opinions on aikido, jazz music, pumpkin pie, and “A Prairie Home Companion.” That I’m not fond of them doesn’t mean they’re bad, it means I’m not as good as I could be.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Worse yet, when I do regularly meditate, I find my life is better. Stress is lower, my health improves. I can focus more on my work, and am less likely to say things I regret to my friends, colleagues, and loved ones. Problems seem smaller. I seem bigger.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;And I’m not alone. Over the past few decades, a host of researchTrusted Source has supported the conclusion that meditation is good for us, and that we should all meditate a few minutes each day.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Digital Society School</name></author><summary type="html">I don’t like meditating. But when I do it regularly, life is better. Stress is lower. My health improves. Problems seem smaller. I seem bigger.</summary></entry></feed>